(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
エルタマ 弁当差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらまめの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Eltama Bento Gift Project Participant List
To all the Soramame who sent gifts, thank you very much!
AZKi メジャーデビュー EP 『3枚目の地図』 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "Sanmaime no Chizu" Now Available!
AZKi 「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover) Now Available!
AZKi 「Sincerely」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Now Available!
ときのそら 2024年3月6日(水) Release
Mini Album 『STAR STAR★T』 リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR STAR★T"
Release Decided for March 6, 2024!
ときのそら 歌ってみた 「可愛くてごめん」 配信中！
Tokino Sora "Kawaikute Gomen" (Cover) Now Available!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム 『Futurity Step』 配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" Now Available!
SorAZ Major Debut Live 『First Gravity』
1月27日(土) CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity"
Jan 27 (Sat) CD Venue Exclusive Benefits
エルタマ 弁当差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらまめの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Eltama Bento Gift Project Participant List
To all the Soramame who sent gifts, thank you very much!
エルタマ 当選差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Eltama Winning Gift Project Participant List
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらとも・開拓者の皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To all the Soratomo and Pioneers who sent gifts, thank you very much!
AZKi メジャーデビューEP 「3枚目の地図」 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" now available!
AZKi 「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover) now available!
AZKi 「Sincerely」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) now available!
ときのそら 2024年3月6日(水) Release Mini Album STAR STAR★T リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album STAR STAR★T to be released on Wed, March 6, 2024!
ときのそら 歌ってみた 「可愛くてごめん」 配信中！
Tokino Sora "Kawaikute Gomen" Cover now available!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム 「Futurity Step」 好評配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" now available!
SorAZ Major Debut Live 「First Gravity」 CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Venue Exclusive Bonus
エルタマ 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Eltama Gift Project Participants List
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらともの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much to all the Soratomos who sent gifts!
AZKi メジャーデビュー EP 『3枚目の地図』 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3-mai me no Chizu" Now Streaming!
AZKi 「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandi Rendezvous" (Cover) Now Streaming!
AZKi 「Sincerely」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Now Streaming!
ときのそら 2024年3月6日(水) Release
Mini Album 『STAR STAR★T』 リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR STAR★T"
Releasing Wednesday, March 6, 2024!
ときのそら 歌ってみた 「可愛くてごめん」 配信中！
Tokino Sora "Kawaisikute Gomen" (Cover) Now Streaming!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム 『Futurity Step』 配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" Now Streaming!
SorAZ Major Debut Live 「First Gravity」
1月27日 (土) CD 物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity"
Saturday, Jan 27 CD Sales Exclusive Bonus
エルタマ 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Eltama Gift Project Participants List
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらともの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much to all the Soratomos who sent gifts!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
"Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover)
「Sincerely」(Cover)
"Sincerely" (Cover)
2024年3月6日(水) Release
Mini Album STAR STAR★T リリース決定！
March 6, 2024 (Wed) Release
Mini Album STAR STAR★T release confirmed!
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Sang "Kawaisugite Gomen" (Cover)
2023.12.20 Release SorAZ
メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
Major Debut Album Futurity Step
Major Debut Live 「First Gravity」
1月27日(土) CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live "First Gravity"
January 27th (Sat) CD physical sales limited benefits
エルタマ 当選差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらともの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Eltema Contribution Project Participants List
To all the Soratomos who sent contributions, thank you very much!
エルタマ 当選差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
差し入れを贈ってくださった開拓者の皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Eltema Contribution Project Participants List
To all the Pioneers who sent contributions, thank you very much!
メジャーデビューEP 「3枚目の地図」 好評配信中！
Major Debut EP "The Third Map" now streaming!
エルタマ 当選差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらめめの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Eltema Contribution Project Participants List
To all the Soramemes who sent contributions, thank you very much!
AZKi 「Sincerely」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi 'Sincerely' (Cover) - Now Streaming!
ときのそら Mini Album STAR STAR★T リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album 'STAR STAR★T' Release Confirmed!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora 'Kawaikute Gomen' Cover - Now Streaming!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step 配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album 'Futurity Step' - Now Streaming!
Major Debut Live「First Gravity」CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live 'First Gravity' CD Venue-Exclusive Bonus
エルタマ 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Eltama Gift Project Participant List
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらまめの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
A huge thank you to all the Soramame who sent us gifts!
本日はSorAZ Major Debut Live『First Gravity』@CLUB CITTA'にご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for coming to SorAZ Major Debut Live 'First Gravity' at CLUB CITTA' today.
開演に先立ちまして、そらまめの皆様にお願いしたいことをお伝えします。
Before the show begins, we have a few requests for all the Soramame fans.
客席内での、モッシュ、ダイブ、ジャンプ等の危険行為は禁止となります。
Dangerous acts such as moshing, diving, and jumping are prohibited in the audience area.
以上のことが守られない場合は、公演を一時中断、もしくは、中止させていただく可能性がございます。
Failure to follow these rules may result in the performance being suspended or cancelled.
ペンライトは周りのお客様のご迷惑にならないよう、ご配慮お願いします。
Please use your penlights considerately so as not to disturb those around you.
頭の上に出したり、大きく左右に振り回すと、後ろのお客様や、周りのお客様のご迷惑となる場合がございます。
Holding them above your head or swinging them widely can obstruct the view of others.
スタッフが注意させていただく場合がございますので、ご了承ください。
Please note that staff may intervene if necessary.
本公演は映像配信、および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、お客様の様子が映り込む場合がございます。
This concert will be filmed and photographed; your image may be included in the footage.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
This footage may be used for promotional purposes. Thank you for your understanding.
客席内での携帯電話、スマートフォンの利用は禁止です。
The use of mobile phones and smartphones is prohibited in the audience area.
携帯電話や音の鳴る機械の電源はあらかじめお切りくださいますようお願い申し上げます。
Please turn off your mobile phones and any devices that make sound.
また、携帯電話、スマートフォン等による撮影、録音、録画は固くお断りします。
Photography, audio recording, and video recording are strictly prohibited.
万が一発見した場合は、データ削除の上、退場していただく場合がございます。
If caught, your data will be deleted, and you may be asked to leave.
最後に、ライブの途中で具合が悪くなったりしたら、お近くのスタッフにお声がけください。
Finally, if you feel unwell during the live, please alert a nearby staff member.
また、地震、火事などの非常時、慌てずスタッフの誘導に従って避難していただきますよう、お願いいたします。
In case of an emergency, please remain calm and follow staff instructions to evacuate.
配信でご視聴のお客様へ。本ライブの録音、録画、ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固くお断りいたします。
To those watching the stream: recording, mirror streaming, and illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
その代わり、スクリーンショットを撮影して映像とともにSNSに投稿していただくことは大歓迎です。
However, we welcome you to take screenshots and post them to SNS along with the footage.
本公演のハッシュタグは #SorAZGravity となります。
The hashtag for today's concert is #SorAZGravity.
もしもしー
Hello?
ねえ、みんな聞こえてますか？
Hey, can everyone hear me?
マイクテスト！
Mic test!
マイクテストだよ！
It's a mic test!
マイクテスト。
Mic test.
みんな...
Everyone...
...聞こえてますかー？
...can you hear us?
見えてるわけないと思う...
I don't think they can see us...
そら、そらから...
From the sky, I, Sora...
...みんなを見守っている...
...am watching over you all...
見えてますかー？
Can you see me?
Can you see us?
多分これから見えます。ときのそらです。
You'll probably be able to see us soon. I'm Tokino Sora.
AZKiです。
I'm AZKi.
まあ、突如としてちょっとお届けしておりますが...
Well, we're suddenly bringing this to you...
ゲリラだよ、ゲリラ！
It's a guerrilla stream!
みんな、今どんな気持ち？
How is everyone feeling right now?
え、そんな聞き方でいいのかな？
Eh, is that the right way to ask?
そんな気持ちをハッシュタグ...
Post those feelings with the hashtag...
...#SorAZGravity でポストしてください！
...#SorAZGravity!
誰かポストしてくれる人ー？
Who's going to post for us?
ありがとう！トレンド入り目指していこう！
Thank you! Let's aim to get trending!
すごい、みんな...
Wow, everyone...
...みんな熱気来てる。
...everyone's so fired up.
タオル振ってくれてる！
You're waving your towels!
あ、タオル、タオル振ってくれてる！
Ah, towels! You're waving your towels!
タオル！
Towels!
暑くない？大丈夫？
Isn't it hot? Are you okay?
暑いの？暑い？
Is it hot? Is it?
これからもっと熱くなりますから。
It's going to get even hotter from now on.
みんな気をつけて。
Everyone, be careful.
あと、みんな仲良く...
Also, everyone get along...
...ぬんぬんしながらライブ見...
...and watch the live while 'nunnun'-ing...
...ね、ライブ楽しんでいこうね。
...and let's enjoy the live!
ぬん！あず！ぬん！あず！
Nun! Azu! Nun! Azu!
じゃあ、みんなもう少し待ってててください。
Well then, everyone, please wait just a little longer.
2023.12.20 Release
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
SorAZ Major Debut Live「First Gravity」
1月27日(土) CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity"
Jan 27 (Sat) CD Merchandise Limited Bonus
エルタマ お祝い差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
El Tama Celebration Gift Project Participant List
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらとめの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To all the Soratome who sent gifts, thank you very much!
エルタマ お祝い差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
El Tama Celebration Gift Project Participant List
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらとめの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To all the Soratome who sent gifts, thank you very much!
AZKi メジャーデビューEP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now Available!
AZKi 「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover) Now Available!
AZKi 「Sincerely」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Now Available!
ときのそら 2024年3月6日(水) Release
Mini Album STAR STAR*T リリース決定！
Tokino Sora 2024.03.06 (Wed) Release
Mini Album STAR STAR*T Confirmed!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora "Kawaikute Gomen" Cover Now Available!
2023.12.20 Release
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
SorAZ Major Debut Live「First Gravity」
1月27日(土) CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity"
Jan 27 (Sat) CD Merchandise Limited Bonus
エルタマ お祝い差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
El Tama Celebration Gift Project Participant List
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらとめの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To all the Soratome who sent gifts, thank you very much!
エルタマ お祝い差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
El Tama Celebration Gift Project Participant List
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらとめの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To all the Soratome who sent gifts, thank you very much!
AZKi メジャーデビューEP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now Available!
AZKi 「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover) Now Available!
AZKi 「Sincerely」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Now Available!
ときのそら 2024年3月6日(水) Release
Mini Album STAR STAR*T リリース決定！
Tokino Sora 2024.03.06 (Wed) Release
Mini Album STAR STAR*T Confirmed!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora "Kawaikute Gomen" Cover Now Available!
2023.12.20 Release
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらまめの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To all the Soramame who sent gifts, thank you very much!
AZKi メジャーデビュー EP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now Streaming!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover) 配信中！
"Tokyo Shandi Rendezvous" (Cover) Now Streaming!
「Sincerely」(Cover) 配信中！
"Sincerely" (Cover) Now Streaming!
ときのそら Mini Album「STAR STAR*T」2024年3月6日(水)リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR STAR*T" - Released March 6, 2024!
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
"Kawaikute Gomen" (Cover) Now Streaming!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」好評配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" Now Streaming!
SorAZ Major Debut Live『First Gravity』CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Merchandise Benefits
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらまめの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To all the Soramame who sent gifts, thank you very much!
AZKi メジャーデビュー EP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now Streaming!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover) 配信中！
"Tokyo Shandi Rendezvous" (Cover) Now Streaming!
「Sincerely」(Cover) 配信中！
"Sincerely" (Cover) Now Streaming!
ときのそら Mini Album「STAR STAR*T」2024年3月6日(水)リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR STAR*T" - Released March 6, 2024!
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
"Kawaikute Gomen" (Cover) Now Streaming!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」好評配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" Now Streaming!
SorAZ Major Debut Live『First Gravity』CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Merchandise Benefits
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらまめの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To all the Soramame who sent gifts, thank you very much!
エルタマ 弁当差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらとも・開拓者の皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Eru-tama Bento Refreshment Plan Participant List
To all the Soratomo and Pioneers who sent refreshments, thank you very much!
AZKi メジャーデビューEP 「3枚目の地図」 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now available!
AZKi 「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandi Rendezvous" (Cover) Now available!
AZKi 「Sincerely」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Now available!
ときのそら Mini Album 「STAR STAR★T」 リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR STAR★T" release decided!
ときのそら 歌ってみた 「可愛くてごめん」 配信中！
Tokino Sora "Kawaikute Gomen" song cover now available!
SorAZ Major Debut Album 「Futurity Step」 好評配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" now available!
SorAZ Major Debut Live 「First Gravity」 CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD sales limited bonus
エルタマ 弁当差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらとも・開拓者の皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Eru-tama Bento Refreshment Plan Participant List
To all the Soratomo and Pioneers who sent refreshments, thank you very much!
AZKi メジャーデビューEP 「3枚目の地図」 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now available!
AZKi 「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandi Rendezvous" (Cover) Now available!
AZKi 「Sincerely」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Now available!
ときのそら Mini Album 「STAR STAR★T」 リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR STAR★T" release decided!
ときのそら 歌ってみた 「可愛くてごめん」 配信中！
Tokino Sora "Kawaikute Gomen" song cover now available!
SorAZ Major Debut Album 「Futurity Step」 好評配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" now available!
SorAZ Major Debut Live 「First Gravity」 CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD sales limited bonus
エルタマ 弁当差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらとも・開拓者の皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Eru-tama Bento Refreshment Plan Participant List
To all the Soratomo and Pioneers who sent refreshments, thank you very much!
AZKi メジャーデビューEP 「3枚目の地図」 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now available!
AZKi 「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandi Rendezvous" (Cover) Now available!
AZKi 「Sincerely」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Now available!
ときのそら Mini Album 「STAR STAR★T」 リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR STAR★T" release decided!
ときのそら 歌ってみた 「可愛くてごめん」 配信中！
Tokino Sora "Kawaikute Gomen" song cover now available!
SorAZ Major Debut Album 「Futurity Step」 好評配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" now available!
SorAZ Major Debut Live 「First Gravity」 CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD sales limited bonus
エルタマ 弁当差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらとも・開拓者の皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Eru-tama Bento Refreshment Plan Participant List
To all the Soratomo and Pioneers who sent refreshments, thank you very much!
AZKi メジャーデビューEP 「3枚目の地図」 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now available!
AZKi 「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandi Rendezvous" (Cover) Now available!
AZKi 「Sincerely」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Now available!
ときのそら Mini Album 「STAR STAR★T」 リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR STAR★T" release decided!
ときのそら 歌ってみた 「可愛くてごめん」 配信中！
Tokino Sora "Kawaikute Gomen" song cover now available!
SorAZ Major Debut Album 「Futurity Step」 好評配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" now available!
SorAZ Major Debut Live 「First Gravity」 CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD sales limited bonus
エルタマ 弁当差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらとも・開拓者の皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Eru-tama Bento Refreshment Plan Participant List
To all the Soratomo and Pioneers who sent refreshments, thank you very much!
AZKi メジャーデビューEP 「3枚目の地図」 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" Now available!
AZKi 「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandi Rendezvous" (Cover) Now available!
AZKi 「Sincerely」 (Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Now available!
ときのそら Mini Album 「STAR STAR★T」 リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR STAR★T" release decided!
ときのそら 歌ってみた 「可愛くてごめん」 配信中！
Tokino Sora "Kawaikute Gomen" song cover now available!
SorAZ Major Debut Album 「Futurity Step」 好評配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" now available!
SorAZ Major Debut Live 「First Gravity」 CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD sales limited bonus
エルタマ 弁当差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらとも・開拓者の皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Eru-tama Bento Refreshment Plan Participant List
To all the Soratomo and Pioneers who sent refreshments, thank you very much!
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらとも・開拓者の皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To all the Soratomo and Pioneers who sent gifts, thank you very much!
AZKi メジャーデビューEP『3枚目の地図』好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "3rd Map" now available!
AZKi「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover) now available!
AZKi「Sincerely」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) now available!
2024年3月6日(水) Release ときのそら Mini Album『STAR STAR*T』リリース決定！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR STAR*T" to be released on Wednesday, March 6, 2024!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora "Kawaii kute Gomen" (Cover) now available!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム『Futurity Step』配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" now available!
SorAZ Major Debut Live『First Gravity』1月27日(土) CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" Jan 27 (Sat) CD store limited benefits
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらとも・開拓者の皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To all the Soratomo and Pioneers who sent gifts, thank you very much!
AZKi メジャーデビューEP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "Sanmaime no Chizu" Now Streaming!
AZKi「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover) Now Streaming!
AZKi「Sincerely」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Now Streaming!
ときのそら Mini Album「STAR STAR★T」2024年3月6日(水) Release！
Tokino Sora Mini Album "STAR STAR★T" Releasing March 6, 2024 (Wed)!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora Sang It: "Kawaikute Gomen" Now Streaming!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" Now Streaming!
SorAZ Major Debut Live『First Gravity』CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Venue Exclusive Bonuses
エルタマ 差し入れ企画参加者様一覧
Eltema Refreshment Project Participant List
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらまめの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you to all the Soramame who sent refreshments!
エルタマ 差し入れ企画参加者様一覧
Eltema Refreshment Project Participant List
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらまめの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you to all the Soramame who sent refreshments!
AZKi メジャーデビューEP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "Sanmaime no Chizu" Now Streaming!
AZKi「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover) Now Streaming!
AZKi 「Sincerely」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Now Available!
（歌）言葉はいつでも...
(Singing) Words are always...
ときのそら 2024年3月6日(水) Release
Mini Album STAR STAR★T リリース決定！
Tokino Sora: New Mini Album "STAR STAR★T"
Releasing March 6, 2024!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora: "Kawaii kute Gomen" (Cover) Now Available!
（歌）chu! 可愛くてごめん
(Singing) Chu! Sorry for being cute
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step 配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" Now Available!
SorAZ Major Debut Live 「First Gravity」 CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Merch Venue Exclusive Benefits
エルタマ 出し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
差し入れを贈ってくださった皆様、ありがとうございます！
El-Tama Gift Box Project Participant List
To everyone who sent gifts, thank you very much!
AZKi メジャーデビューEP 「3枚目の地図」 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "Sanmai me no Chizu" Now Available!
AZKi 「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover) Now Available!
（歌）トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ...
(Singing) Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous...
AZKi 「Sincerely」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Sincerely" (Cover) Now Available!
ときのそら 2024年3月6日(水) Release
Mini Album STAR STAR★T リリース決定！
Tokino Sora: New Mini Album "STAR STAR★T"
Releasing March 6, 2024!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora: "Kawaii kute Gomen" (Cover) Now Available!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step 配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" Now Available!
SorAZ Major Debut Live 「First Gravity」 CD物販限定特典
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Merch Venue Exclusive Benefits
エルタマ 出し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
差し入れを贈ってくださった皆様、ありがとうございます！
El-Tama Gift Box Project Participant List
To everyone who sent gifts, thank you very much!
AZKi メジャーデビューEP 「3枚目の地図」 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP "Sanmai me no Chizu" Now Available!
AZKi 「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover) Now Available!
2024年3月6日(水) Release Mini Album STAR STAR★T リリース決定！
Mini Album STAR STAR★T Release Confirmed for March 6, 2024!
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Cover Song 'Kawaikute Gomen' Now Streaming!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step 配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album 'Futurity Step' Now Streaming!
Major Debut Live「First Gravity」CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live 'First Gravity' CD Venue Exclusive Benefit
エルクマ お裾分け差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Erukuma Gift Contribution Project Participant List
AZKi メジャーデビューEP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP 'The 3rd Map' Now Streaming!
AZKi 「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi 'Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous' (Cover) Now Streaming!
AZKi 「Sincerely」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi 'Sincerely' (Cover) Now Streaming!
せーのっで せーのっで
One, two... One, two...
深呼吸
Take a deep breath
始まっていくここから ready go!
Starting from here, ready go!
みんな来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you all for coming!
SorAZだよー！
It's SorAZ!
大気圏 すり抜けて
Slipping through the atmosphere
イメージも 歌声も
Our images and our voices
意識を 飛び越えて 響く
Resonating beyond consciousness
照らし出す 宇宙中
Illuminating the whole universe
漂い 巡り会い
Drifting and meeting one another
瞬間 ドキする 奇跡って
In a moment, a heart-pounding miracle
高まって
Getting faster
くるくる 回る みんな まるで
Spinning round and round, everyone just like
私たちの夢のファーストプレス
Our dream's first press
思い切り 遊ぼう
Let's play as much as we can
A to Z 宙を駆けて 振り切っちゃって go!
A to Z, racing through the sky, shaking it off, go!
化学反応で 生み出す光
A light created by a chemical reaction
今ここで 繋がった
Connected right here, right now
照らして 照らし合って
Illuminating, reflecting each other
せーのっで 頷いて
One, two, and nod
始まっていく ワンダー ready go!
Beginning the wonder, ready go!
二番も行くよー！
Let's go for the second verse too!
ときめき タップして
Tapping into the excitement
開くわ 新時代
Opening a new era
可能性 その身は なんて
Possibility, that body is just
二人の エーテルに
To the ether of the two of us
ドキドキ 伝播する
The heart-throbbing spreads
解釈 一致でしょ 生きるって
It's a shared interpretation, right? To live is
運命の シンコペーション
The syncopation of destiny
星屑 Runaway から 投げて
Throwing from a stardust runaway
未知の彼方 光る フューチャーサイン
A future sign shining from the unknown
キャッチして Role a
Catch it and roll a
愛という 奏でるのは ミラクル系
Playing something called love, a miracle-type
以心伝心で パルス 照らす
Illuminating pulses by heart-to-heart communication
今という 瞬間を
The moment called now
感じて 感じ合って
Feel it, feel each other
せーのっで 深呼吸
One, two, take a deep breath
見たことない ワンダー 君と
A wonder never seen before, with you
思いと思いが 作る世界
The world created by our shared feelings
ここにある ここにいるよ 歌を
It's here, I'm here, the song is here
歌えば 一つになれる
If we sing, we can become one
もっとなれるよ 自由に
We can become more free
ようこそ ここは バイスのない
Welcome, there is no bias here
二人のエキスポ グラビスペイシー
Our Expo, Gravi-Spacy!
私たちの夢のファーストプレス
Our dream's first press
思い切り 遊ぼう
Let's play as much as we can
A to Z 宙を駆けて 振り切っちゃって go!
A to Z, racing through the sky, shaking it off, go!
化学反応で 生み出す光
A light created by a chemical reaction
今ここで 繋がった
Connected right here, right now
照らして 照らし合って
Illuminating, reflecting each other
せーのっで 深呼吸
One, two, take a deep breath
どこまでも 行こうよ
Let's go as far as we can
せーのっで 頷いて
One, two, and nod
始まっていく ワンダー ready go!
Beginning the wonder, ready go!
まだまだ昼だけど盛り上がって！
It's still daytime, but let's get hyped!
次の曲も行っちゃおう！
Let's move on to the next song too!
察した 向こう側の気配
I sensed a presence on the other side
きっと 目に映そう
I'm sure it'll come into view
ごまかしすぎて 言葉積み重ねよう
Too much deception, let's stack words instead
高すぎる壁さえも 飛んでしまうかな
I wonder if we'll even leap over walls that are too high
通り抜けたって 何も楽しくないって
Even if we pass through, it wouldn't be any fun
Never 君が教えてくれていたんだ
Never, you were the one who taught me that
夢を散々掛け合わせ 時にそう間違って
Multiplying our dreams time and again, and sometimes making mistakes
それもラフに気にせずに
Don't mind it, just take it easy
何度でも挑もう
Let's keep challenging ourselves
だって I'm my self
Because I'm myself
意味のない評価で
Don't compare the world
世界比べないで
with meaningless evaluations
叶えたい本音は
The true feelings I want to fulfill
全てを包み込む太陽
are like a sun that envelops everything
いっそ好き放題上を目指して
Might as well aim for the top as much as I want
立ちはだかる壁を登って
Climbing the walls that stand in our way
刻んでいきたいな
I want to carve it all out
そして次に望む
And then, looking forward to the next
越えたあの未来
That future we moved beyond
(ハイ！ハイ！)
(Hai! Hai!)
想像したら
When I imagined it
鼓動が聞こえたんだ
I could hear my heartbeat
作り込んだ道なんて
Let's cast aside all the pre-made paths
全部脱ぎ捨て行こう
and go
響く音のまま
Just as the sound resonates
心が赴くまま
Just as the heart dictates
ずっと君なら君なら
If it's you, with you
一緒に何でも築ける
we can build anything together forever
つまずいて視界が
Even if I stumble
何も見えなくなっても
and my vision goes dark
振り向いて笑える
There's a place where I can
そんな場所がある
look back and smile
ただの星も
Even an ordinary star
夢を燦々掛け合わせ
by combining dreams brilliantly
時にそう間違って
Sometimes making mistakes like that
それもラフに気にせずに
Don't mind it, just take it easy
何度でも挑もう
Let's keep challenging ourselves
いつも be yourself
Always be yourself
試さないとほら
Look, if you don't try
何も始まらない
nothing will ever start
些細な勇気で
Until we change tomorrow
明日を変えるまでもっと
with just a little courage, even more
意味のない評価で
Don't compare the world
世界比べないで
with meaningless evaluations
叶えたい本音は
The true feelings I want to fulfill
全てを包み込む太陽
are like a sun that envelops everything
いっそ好き放題上を目指して
Might as well aim for the top as much as I want
立ちはだかる壁を登って
Climbing the walls that stand in our way
刻んでいきたいな
I want to carve it all out
そして次に望む
And then, looking forward to the next
越えたあの未来
That future we moved beyond
Reduct and Saturate the future
(ハイ！ハイ！)
(Hai! Hai!)
初めから僕らは繋がっていたんだ
We've been connected from the very start
引力で出会えたのは必然
Meeting through gravity was inevitable
君も気づいているのかな
I wonder if you've noticed too
遥か宇宙から見た
From far out in space
僕らはまるでちっぽけな星屑
we look like tiny stardust
君と出会えた瞬間に
The moment I met you
僕ら星座になれたの
we became a constellation
時間を超えて Don't stop 未来へ
Beyond time, don't stop, to the future
二つ重ねて超絶ミラクル
Overlap the two for a transcendental miracle
誰も止められない魔法を
A magic that nobody can stop
レベチの僕らの銀河パーティーナイト
Our next-level galaxy party night
二人は Destiny
The two of us are Destiny
引力に惹かれ弾ける Community
Drawn by gravity, a bursting community
ドキドキして 愛して
With a pounding heart, love me
Now ワクワクして
and now get excited
二人のラプソディ
Our rhapsody
宇宙のままに So Dance Music
just as the universe is, so dance music
すれ違いも Step together
Even when passing each other, step together
始めようぜ僕らの Gravity
Let's start our Gravity
見つめてた朝来るまで
I was staring until the morning came
これが完全無欠なイリュージョン
This is the absolute, flawless illusion
まさに完璧なフュージョン
Truly the perfect fusion
歌い踊ればソリューション
Singing and dancing is the solution
ここは僕たちなりの Region
This is our own region
みんなの力が重なり広がる
Everyone's power overlaps and expands
たった一つのユニバース
Into one single universe
ねえ ちょっと泣いたって明日は晴れる
Hey, even if you cry a little, tomorrow will be clear
Take it easy ひとりでいないで
Take it easy, don't be alone
Hold on 繋がる いつでも 未来で
Hold on, we're always connected in the future
Let me up
二人の心拍数
Our heart rates
求め合う鼓動が今 faster
heartbeats seeking each other, are getting faster now
見逃さないで
Don't look away.
感じて
Feel it.
虜になって
Be captivated.
これぞインフィニティ
This is infinity.
考える前に
Before you think,
Just do it
自分でも怖い鼓動で
With a heartbeat that scares even me,
これからが僕らのグラビティ
this is our gravity from now on.
ついてきて　辿り着くまで　Yeah
Follow me until we arrive, yeah!
何回でも星座を作るよ
We'll create constellations again and again,
二人で
the two of us together.
幾分の想像を越えて
Going beyond imagination many times over,
未来へ
towards the future.
Wow Wow
二人はデスティニー
The two of us are destiny.
強くなる絆はまだ　So going
Our bond keeps growing stronger, so going.
ドキドキして
My heart is pounding.
明日をワクワクして
Excited for tomorrow.
二人のグラビティ
The gravity of the two of us.
勝ちたいんだ　でも　All right
I want to win, but it's all right.
済ました顔で　また　New beat
With a cool face, a new beat again.
始めようぜ僕らのグラビティ
Let's start our gravity.
見つめてて　朝が来るまで　Yeah
Keep watching us until morning comes, yeah!
こんそらー！
Kon-Sora!
こんあずきー！
Kon-AZKi!
二人合わせて…
The two of us together...
せーの！SorAZです！
One, two! We are SorAZ!
やー！お待たせしました。
Yeah! Sorry to keep you waiting.
お待たせしました、皆さん。
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone.
本日はSorAZ Major Debut Live『First Gravity』
Thank you for coming to the SorAZ Major Debut Live
at CLUB CITTA' 昼公演にお越しいただき
"First Gravity" at CLUB CITTA' afternoon performance.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
みんなかなりお待たせしちゃったね、待ってくれてたの？
We kept you all waiting for quite a while.
待ってくれてたのー？
Were you waiting for us?
今日はね、満員ということで、みんな体調には気を付けて
It's a full house today, so please take care of yourselves
ぜひ最後まで楽しんでいってくださいね。
and enjoy the show until the very end.
みんなありがとう、来てくれて！
Thank you everyone for coming!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
すごい綺麗、ありがとう、ありがとう。
It's so beautiful. Thank you, thank you.
ということで…
So...
えっと、最初にお知らせしておきましょうか。
Um, let's make an announcement first.
最初に空の…
First, from Sora...
ここでYouTubeの無料配信は終わりになります。
The free YouTube broadcast will end here.
もっと見たいなと…
If you want to see more...
始まったばかり！
It's just started!
もっと見たいなと思ってくれたそこのあなた！
To those of you who want to see more!
はい！ありがとう、ありがとう。
Yes! Thank you, thank you.
はい、ぜひですね、えっと概要欄かな？
Yes, please check the description box.
あとコメントにもあるかな？ここ！ここ！
Or maybe in the comments? Here! Here!
はい、ぜひ配信チケットご購入いただいて
Please purchase a streaming ticket
続きもぜひ見てください！
and watch the rest of the show!
見てねー！
Check it out!
スッ…スッ…
(Panting sounds)
どうなったかな？
How was it?
冒頭無料はこちらで終了です。
The free preview ends here.
本編続きをご視聴されたい方は、チケットぴあにてご購入お願いします。
If you wish to watch the rest of the main performance, please purchase a ticket on Ticket Pia.
冒頭無料はこちらで終了です。
本編続きをご視聴されたい方は、
チケットぴあにてご購入お願いします。
The free preview ends here.
If you wish to continue watching the main show,
please purchase your ticket at Ticket Pia.
冒頭無料はこちらで終了です。
本編続きをご視聴されたい方は、チケットぴあにてご購入お願いします。
The free preview ends here. To watch the full show,
please buy a ticket on Ticket Pia.
冒頭無料はこちらで終了です。
本編続きをご視聴されたい方は、チケットぴあにてご購入お願いします。
The free preview ends here.
If you would like to continue watching the full performance, please purchase a ticket on Ticket Pia.
冒頭無料はこちらで終了です。
The free preview ends here.
本編続きをご視聴されたい方は、
If you would like to watch the rest of the show,
チケットぴあにてご購入お願いします。
please purchase a ticket on Ticket Pia.
冒頭無料はこちらで終了です。
本編続きをご視聴されたい方は、チケット(ぴあ)にてご購入お願いします。
The free preview ends here.
If you wish to watch the rest of the concert, please purchase a ticket on Ticket Pia.